https://creativecreek.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://creativecreek.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Creative Creek, LLC will never rent, sell, or give away your personal information. The information will only be used to process orders you make or to interact with you for support purposes. From time to time, we may send you e-mail notifications of new products, upgrades to products you own or other similar correspondence. If you do not wish to receive such e-mail correspondence, just let us know via our contact form and we will be happy to remove your name from our lists.
Cookies
We use cookies on occasion to record session information and past activity.
Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available in your web browser settings.
Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.
Security
Interactions with this web site use an SSL certificate to ensure secure transmission of your information (look for the lock icon in your browser window and a URL that starts with https://)
What rights you have over your data
If you have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
When you use our contact form, your e-mail address, name and comments are set to us via e-mail so that we can respond directly to you. We may retain that e-mail you send indefinitely.
Username or Email Address
Password
Remember Me
Search for:
Search for:
